A Finding Aid to the Jacques Lipchitz papers and Bruce Bassett papers concerning Jacques Lipchitz, 1910-2001, bulk 1941-2001, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Bruce Bassett papers concerning Jacques Lipchitz, 1961-2001; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 43.3 Linear feet Boxes 13-67, OV 68-69
  - Film Projects Regarding Jacques Lipchitz, 1971-2001; 2.5; Archival Resource Key; 28.2 Linear feet Boxes 22-46, 53-65, OV 69
    - Original Footage and Stock Footage, 1971-1981; 2.5.1; Archival Resource Key
      - Italy Filming, Archival Resource Key
        - Sound reels # 167-171, 1971; Archival Resource Key; 5 Sound tape reels (Box 26, Item 1-5)
        - Dubbed sound reels #1-13, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key; 13 Sound tape reels (Box 26, Item 6-18)
          (A key to original reels contained on each dub reel is found with dub reel 1, box 5, item 6.)
        - Interview of Lipchitz by Bruce Bassett, 1971 June 24; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel (Box 26, Item 19)
          (A pre-production interview, about the pending Metropolitan Museum exhibition)
        - Lipchitz Interview Re-takes, 1972 April 29; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel (Box 26, Item 20)
        - Interview with Jacques Lipchitz, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel (Box 26, Item 21)
          (Excerpts)
        - Florence Section Narration, undated; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel (Box 26, Item 22)
        - Lipchitz Working in Clay, Sync Sound, undated; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel (Box 26, Item 23)
        - Archival Reel 31, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel workprint picture 16mm (Item FC 38)
          (Original camera reel 137)
        - Archival Reel 32, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel workprint picture 16mm (Item FC 39)
          (Original camera reels 145-146)
        - Archival Reel 33, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel workprint picture 16mm (Item FC 40)
          (Original camera reels 148-150)
        - Archival Reel 34, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel workprint picture 16mm (Item FC 41)
          (Original camera reel 152)
        - Archival Reel 35, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel workprint picture 16mm (Item FC 42)
          (Original camera reel 163)
        - Archival Reel 37, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel workprint picture 16mm (Item FC 43)
          (Original camera reels 181-182)
        - Archival Reel 38, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel workprint picture 16mm (Item FC 44)
          (Original camera reels 184-186)
        - Archival Reel 39, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel workprint picture 16mm (Item FC 45)
          (Original camera reels 187-188)
        - Archival Reel 40, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel workprint picture 16mm (Item FC 46)
          (Original camera reels 189-191)
        - Archival Reel 41, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel workprint picture 16mm (Item FC 47)
          (Original camera reels 192-193)
        - Archival Reel 31, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel soundtrack, Contains Magnetic Track 16mm (Item FC 48)
          (original sound reel 131)
        - Archival Reel 32, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel soundtrack, Contains Magnetic Track 16mm (Item FC 49)
          (Original sound reel 139-140)
        - Archival Reel 33, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel soundtrack, Contains Magnetic Track 16mm (Item FC 50)
          (Original sound reel 142-144)
        - Archival Reel 35, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel soundtrack, Contains Magnetic Track 16mm (Item FC 51)
          (Original sound reel 152)
        - Archival Reel 37, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel soundtrack, Contains Magnetic Track 16mm (Item FC 52)
          (Original sound reels 158-159)
        - Archival Reel 38, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel soundtrack, Contains Magnetic Track 16mm (Item FC 53)
          (Original sound reels 162, 164)
        - Archival Reel 39, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel soundtrack, Contains Magnetic Track (Item FC 54)
          (Original sound reels 166-167)
        - Archival Reel 40, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel soundtrack, Contains Magnetic Track 16mm (Item FC 55)
          (Original sound reels 167-169)
        - Archival Reel 41, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel soundtrack, Contains Magnetic Track 16mm (Item FC 56)
          (Original sound reels 170-171)
        - Lipchitz Working on His Sculpture The Last Embrace, circa 1972; Archival Resource Key; 2 Film reels 2 film reels: picture (Item FC 57-58)
          - Lipchitz working on Last Embrace, reel 1, 1972; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 58)
          - Lipchitz working on Last Embrace, reel 2, 1972; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 57)
      - Lipchitz Sculpture at the Metropolitan Museum, 1972; Archival Resource Key; Film reels 4 film reels: picture (Item FC 250-251)
        - Sculpture at the Metropolitan Museum, 1972; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 59)
        - Sculpture filmed at MET, 1978; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 60)
      - Index to Sculptures Filmed at the Metropolitan Museum, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 24)
        Index on paper, 1 folder
      - Selected Sculptures, European Shoot, undated; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (U-matic) (Box 26, Item 26)
      - Philadelphia Installation and Dedication of Government of the People, 1976-1977; Archival Resource Key (Item 252-259)
        - Philadelphia Installation and Dedication of Government of the People, 1976-1977; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel (Box 26, Folder 27)
        - Philadelphia Installation reel 1, 1976-1977; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 61)
        - Philadelphia Installation reel 2, 1976-1977; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 62)
        - Philadelphia Installation reel 3, 1976-1977; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 63)
        - Philadelphia Installation reel 4, 1976-1977; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 64)
        - Philadelphia Installation reel 5, 1976-1977; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 65)
        - Philadelphia Installation reel 6, 1976-1977; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 66)
        - Philadelphia Installation reel 7, 1976-1977; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 67)
        - Philadelphia Installation reel 8, 1976-1977; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 68)
        - Philadelphia Installation reel 9, 1976-1977; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 69)
        - Philadelphia Installation reel 10, 1976-1977; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 70)
      - New York Installation of Bellerophon Taming Pegasus, 1977 April; Archival Resource Key; (8 film reels: sound on film, 1 film reel: picture) (Item FC 260-268)
        - New York Installation of Bellerophon Taming Pegasus, 1977 April; Archival Resource Key; 6 Sound tape reels (Box 26, Folder 28-30)
        - New York Installation of Bellerophon Taming Pegasus, 1977-04; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound tape reels (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Interview with Yulla Lipchitz, 1977 May; Archival Resource Key
        Picture only, no sound
        - Interview with Yulla Lipchitz, reel 1, 1977; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 71)
      - Italian Foundry Filming, 1977 August; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel (Item FC 72)
      - Miami Interview with Joe Harrison, 1977; Archival Resource Key
        (See also series 5.2, Segments)
        - Miami Interview with Joe Harrison, 1977; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel (Box 27, Folder 2)
        - Miami Interview with Joe Harrison, 1977; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 73)
      - Israel Filming, 1977-1978; Archival Resource Key
        - Israel Filming, Reel 1, bulk 1977-1978; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel Contains Magnetic Track 16mm (Item FC 74)
      - Unidentified Aerial Footage, undated; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 75)
      - Sound Effects and Titles, undated; Archival Resource Key; 9 Film reels (9 film reels: 35mm magnetic sound loop, 1 film reel: 16mm magnetic sound loop, 2 film reels: 35mm picture; film housed in 1 film can) (Item FC 76-78)
      - Stills and Animation, undated; Archival Resource Key; (5 film reels in 1 film can) (Item FC 80-83)
        - Stills and Animations, reel 1, 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 79)
      - Stock Footage, undated; Archival Resource Key; (6 film reels in 1 film can) (Item FC 85-89)
        - Lipchitz Stock Footage, aerial A-roll, 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 84)
    - Jacques Lipchitz Interactive Project, 1972-2001; 2.5.2; Archival Resource Key
      This subseries contains the edited film and video created for the Lipchitz interactive project, as well as paper records documenting the production and presentation of its various installations.
      Audiovisual materials include multiple versions of "answers" compiled from the Lipchitz interviews filmed in 1971, used in multiple interactive installations between 1972 and 2001. Each version exists in a group of 2 to 4 reels or tapes, in its source format of motion picture film, or its installation format of various video types. Each group and its elements is described using the reel names and numbers assigned by Bassett to maintain their connection to paper documentation, and groups are arranged chronologically. The item headings listed below are direct transcriptions of Bassett's labels. Six miscellaneous reels, which do not appear to belong to any of the main groups of film reels, are arranged after the dated reels. Although they may duplicate some of the dated material, these miscellaneous reels were found to be in better condition than some of their copies, so they were retained.
      Also found are 117 small film and soundtrack reels of named segments whose titles correspond to segments listed in the source books. These may be outtakes or workprint of the edited Lipchitz answers.
      Paper records in this series include the original questions generated by the public during installations of the interactive project. Questions exist in multiple forms including orignal handwritten cards and printouts in multiple sets, each with a different arrangement of data. Notebooks include mainly technical and shot notes, but also notes on an Andy Goldsworthy interview. Production files contain detailed notes on the assembly of segments and revisions to the reels, including a negative pull list for a recent revision. The Program Guide contains annotated indexes to segments on each reel or disc, and other technical notes.
      Source Books, found in the paper documentation, provide a scene-by-scene content inventory and transcript of the audiovisual material in each version presented to the public between 1972 and 2001. They also contain notes related to the operation of the interactive program. Although all of the source books contain redundant and similar content, each version has its own annotations and a variety of interfiled production records specific to its particular installation. The 2001 source book from the Krannert Art Museum installation also includes a disc directory, photographs of sculptures in the Krannert exhibit, and an article on Lipchitz.
      Technical drawings show the way the video equipment was set up in the installations, showing a user in relation to the interactive system display. The Transcript folder includes a collection of Lipchitz's comments on Pablo Picasso gathered from the footage, a portion of which appears to have been licensed to another production company in the 1980s.
      The chronological arrangement of audiovisual materials in this series has been altered slightly due to the size and physical requirements of the objects.
      - Audiovisual Materials, Archival Resource Key
        - Introduction, circa 1972; Archival Resource Key; (2 film reels: workprint and soundtrack; oversized workprint in Box 57, oversized soundtrack in Box 58) (Item FC 277 and 279)
          - Introduction soundtrack, 1972; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel Contains Magnetic Track 16mm (Item FC 279)
        - Birth-Cubism, circa 1972; Archival Resource Key; (2 film reels: workprint and soundtrack; oversized workprint in Box 57, oversized soundtrack in Box 58) (Item FC 278 and 280)
          - Birth-Cubism soundtrack, 1972; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel Contains Magnetic Track 16mm (Item FC 280)
        - Transparencies-Jacob and the Angel, Circa 1972; Archival Resource Key
          - Transparencies-Jacob and the Angel, circa 1972; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (U-matic) (Box 27, Folder 3)
          - Transparencies - Jacob soundtrack, 1972; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel Contains Magnetic Track 16mm (Item FC 281)
          - Transparencies - Jacob workprint, 1972; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 282)
        - Mother-Virgin, circa 1972; Archival Resource Key; (2 film reels: workprint and soundtrack; oversized workprint in Box 59, oversized soundtrack in Box 60) (Item FC 283-284)
          - Mother-Virgin workprint, 1972; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 283)
          - Mother-Virgin soundtrack, 1972; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel Contains Magnetic Track 16mm (Item FC 284)
        - Reel 1, Part 1, 1972; Archival Resource Key
          - Reel A, Part 1, 1972; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel (Box 27, Folder 4)
          - Reel A, Part 1, A-roll picture, 1972; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 90)
          - Reel A, Part 1, B-roll picture, 1972; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 91)
        - Reel A, Part 2, 1972; Archival Resource Key
          - Reel A, Part 2, 1972; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel (Box 27, Folder 4)
          - Reel A, Part 2, A-roll picture, 1972; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 92)
          - Reel A, Part 2, B-roll picture, 1972; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 93)
        - Reel B, Part 1, 1972; Archival Resource Key
          - Reel B, Part 1, 1972; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel (Box 27, Folder 5)
          - Reel B, Part 1, A-roll picture, 1972; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 94)
          - Reel B, Part 1, B-roll picture, 1972; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 95)
        - Reel B, Part 2, 1972; Archival Resource Key
          - Reel B, Part 2, 1972; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel (Box 27, Folder 5)
          - Reel B, Part 2, A-roll picture, 1972; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 96)
          - Reel B, Part 2, B-roll picture, 1972; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 97)
        - Unidentified Reel, 1972; Archival Resource Key
          - Unidentified reel, A-roll picture, 1972; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 98)
          - Unidentified reel, B-roll picture, 1972; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 99)
        - Reel D, 1979; Archival Resource Key; 2 Videocassettes (U-matic) 1 with visible time code (Box 27, Folder 6)
        - Reels A-D, 1979; Archival Resource Key; 4 Videocassettes (BetacamSP) (Box 27, Folder 7-10)
        - Discs I, circa 1982; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (U-matic) (Box 27, Folder 11)
        - Disc II, Circa 1982; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (U-matic) (Box 28, Folder 1)
        - Discs I-IV, 1999; Archival Resource Key; 4 Videocassettes (Digital Betacam) (Box 28, Folder 2-5)
        - Reel A, 1982; Archival Resource Key; (2 film reels: workprint, 2 film reels: soundtrack) (Item FC 100-103)
        - Reel B, 1982; Archival Resource Key; (2 film reels: workprint, 2 film reels: soundtrack) (Item FC 104-107)
        - Reel C, 1982; Archival Resource Key; 2 Film reels (1 film reel: workprint, 1 film reel: soundtrack; oversized workprint in Box 61, oversized soundtrack reel in Box 60) (Item FC 285 and 287)
          - Reel C soundtrack, 1982; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel Contains Magnetic Track 16mm (Item FC 285)
        - Reel D, 1982; Archival Resource Key; 2 Film reels (1 film reel: workrpint, 1 film reel: soundtrack; oversized workrpint in Box 61, oversized soundtrack reel in Box 60) (Item FC 286 and 288)
          - Reel D soundtrack, 1982; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel Contains Magnetic Track 16mm (Item FC 286)
          - Reel D workprint, 1982; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 288)
        - Miscellaneous Reels, Archival Resource Key
          - Monitor Station Segments, undated; Archival Resource Key
            - Monitor Station Segments, undated; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel (Box 28, Folder 6)
            - Monitor Station Segments, undated; Archival Resource Key; (2 film reels: internegative and answer print) (Item FC 108-109)
          - Met, undated; Archival Resource Key; (2 film reels: workprint and sountrack) (Item FC 110-111)
          - Reel C, Part 1, undated; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel workprint (Item FC 112)
            (Note on original can: "does not contain Picasso")
          - Q+A Reel C, 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel picture 16mm (Item FC 289)
          - Reel II, Part 1, n.d.; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 290)
            (Leader also labeled "D Reel")
          - Unidentified Reel, undated; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel workprint (Item FC 113)
        - Segments, Archival Resource Key
          - Art Is Eternal, Banker's Economy, Bellerophon, circa 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; (4 film reels: workprint, in 1 film can) (Item FC 114-117)
          - Bellerophon, circa 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel (6 film reels: workprint, in 2 film cans) 16mm (Item FC 121-123)
            - Bus to Columbia, 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 118)
            - Pegasus, 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 119)
            - Pegasus, Parking Lot, Buildings, 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 120)
          - Birth and Unity, circa 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; (3 film reels: workprint, in 1 film can) (Item FC 124-126)
          - Columbine, circa 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; (2 film reels: workprint, in 1 oversized film can in Box 63) (Item FC 291-292)
            - Columbine Workprint, reel 1, 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC291)
            - Columbine Workprint, reel 2, 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 292)
          - Cubism, End Section, FF, First Come to America, Florence, Freeze, Government of the People, circa 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel (7 film reels: workprint, in 1 film can) (Item FC 128-133)
            - Govt. of the People (picture), 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 127)
          - Government of the People, circa 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel (3 film reels: workprint, in 1 film can) (Item FC 135-136)
            - Government of the People, Phila., 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 134)
          - Gursenski, James Joyce, circa 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key
            - Gursenski Segment workprint, 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 137)
            - Gursenski Segment original shots, 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 138)
            - James Joyce Segment workprint, 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 139)
            - James Joyce Segment original shots, 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 140)
          - Last Embrace, circa 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; (4 film reels: workprint, in 1 oversized film can in Box 63) (Item FC 294-296)
            - workprint pix, Statements #1 and 2, 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 293)
          - Man Getting Better, Miami and Joe Harrison Interview, circa 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm
            - Miami Museum MOS, 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 141)
            - Bruce Bassett Miami Interview, 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 142)
            - Museum Tracks, 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 144)
            - Marx-Bette, 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 143)
          - Miami and Joe Harrison Interview, Mother and Child, Notre Dame de Liesse, circa 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel (5 film reels: workprint, in 1 film can) (Item FC 146-149)
            - Notre Dame de Liesse (picture), reel 1, 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 145)
          - New Segments, Opening, Paracelles, Pollution Affects Art, Storytelling, circa 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; (7 film reels: workprint, in 1 film can) (Item FC 150-156)
          - Yulla Lipchitz/Israel, circa 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel (6 film reels: workprint, in 1 oversized film can in Box 64) (Item FC 298-299)
            - Yulla/Israel (workprint), reel 1, 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Item FC 297)
          - Unidentified Segments, circa 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; (7 film reels: workprint, in 1 film can) (Item FC 157-163)
        - Miscellaneous Trims (picture and soundtrack), circa 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel combined reels which include the following titles: #30, #83, #144B, #39, 81E and 81F, #97, #3, #62, 144C, #109, #63, #99 and 100, #103, 76C Bruce, 80H Larush, 81F, 80E c.c., 144B, 143 and 144, 271, #54, #60, 81A and 81B, #80 Modis 1917, 272, #80 Modig Nate, 80E, #75, #801, #806 Modig Larush, 144G, #228, #24, #66 and #59, 77, #2, Yulla 16mm (Item FC 164)
          workprint and soundtrack in 1 reel
        - Segments, continued, Archival Resource Key
          - Art Is Eternal, Banker's Economy, Bellerophon, circa 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; (5 film reels: soundtrack, in 1 film can) (Item FC 165-169)
          - Bellerophon, circa 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; (4 film reels: soundtrack, in 1 film can) (Item FC 170-173)
          - Birth and Unity, circa 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; (4 film reels: soundtrack, in 1 film can) (Item FC 174-177)
          - Birth and Unity, Cubism, FF, First come to America, circa 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel (5 film reels: soundtrack, in 1 film can) (Item FC 179-182)
            - Birth and Unity-First Come to America (sound), reel 1, 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel Contains Magnetic Track 16mm (Item FC 178)
          - Gursenski, James Joyce, Last Embrace, circa 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel (6 film reels: soundtrack, in 1 film can) (Item FC 184-188)
            - Gursenski-Last Embrace (sound), 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel Contains Magnetic Track 16mm (Item FC 183)
          - Man Getting Better, Miami and Joe Harrison, circa 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; (3 film reels: soundtrack, in 1 film can) (Item FC 189-191)
          - New Segments, Notre Dame de Liesse, Pollution Affects Art, Storytelling, circa 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; (6 film reels: soundtrack, in 1 film can) (Item FC 192-197)
          - New Segments, Transparencies/Jacob and the Angel, Yulla/Israel, circa 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; (6 film reels: soundtrack, in 1 oversized film can in Box 64) (Item FC 300-305)
          - Unidentified Segments, circa 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key; 13 Film reels soundtrack, in 2 film cans (Item FC 200-210)